[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 21]
Tell me.
What did you want me to come over for?
I never drink alcohol.
Really?
You never tried it?
You are afraid to face it.
And you dare not drink this.
You're afraid that after drinking it,
you'll become Lu Li again.
That's right.
Here.
How is she?
You didn't allow her to stay in Xiyin Mountain,
so I let Master take her away.
I don't know where she is now.
But he will take good care of her.
Won't you go and see her?
Since she has decided to leave,
I don't think I should bother her anymore.
It was you and Immortal Master Wanwu
who drove her away, okay?
Don't you admit it? So hypocritical.
It's been two days.
You obviously can't take it.
Can't you just stop planting this grass?
Now you can no longer stay in Immortal Palace
and will leave tomorrow.
That cruel man wouldn't even come to see you.
Why do you care so much?
Immortal Master?
Immortal Master.
Immortal Master!
Help! Anyone here?
Something happened to Immortal Master!
Help!
This hairpin is for you.
What are you doing?
How about it?
This hairpin belongs to your palace, right?
Do you recognize it?
Yes.
I thought it was too plain,
so I gave it to someone else.
Who did you give it to?
I don't remember.
Shang Yurong.
Why are you still
playing dumb?
I saw
you gave this hairpin to Liu Shao.
No way.
It can't be her.
Why not?
To be honest,
she didn't do anything harmful.
But she was humiliated, tortured and driven away.
Anyone else would be resentful.
Now that she was in despair,
it was not surprising
that she had the idea of killing someone.
His cultivation is much stronger than Liu Shao.
There is demon poison on this hairpin.
And there are no signs of a fight in the room.
It was possible
if she did it while he was off guard.
Energy pill?
Immortal Master is indeed seriously injured,
and his pulse is weak.
But
you'll
also hurt yourself
by doing so.
Even if you don't want to wrong Liu Shao,
you don't have to do such crazy thing.
Cut the crap.
Activate Tai Chu to help me.
Don't worry.
The Weirui Grass has almost grown up.
At most two days,
I
will definitely send it
to that cruel man.
Master,
I'm counting on you then.
It's been three days now.
I really have to go.
Girl,
you should hurry down the mountain.
When I'm free,
I'll go to the human world to see you.
I've seen enough of
these cruel people here as well.
So we'll see each other again soon?
Don't cry.
If you keep crying, this Weirui Grass will be pickled by your tears.
I... these are not tears.
It's herbal juice.
I'm leaving then.
Luo Ge.
What's the matter?
Is this yours?
This seems to be the hairpin Shang Yurong gave me.
Immortal Master Wanwu of Palace Wuji was assassinated,
and the murder weapon was this white jade hairpin.
When Immortal Master wakes up,
we will find out
whether you did this or not.
Luo Ge
can't help you either.
I don't need his help.
I just need him
to believe me.
Are you trying to get him to break his rules to trust you?
Liu Shao,
you really think of him as your family?
Immortal belongs to the Three Realms.
But Immortal
is also that affectionate Luo Ge.
I know what kind of person he is.
Even if I don't love him anymore.
Even if
I don't love him the way I love Lu Li.
But at least,
he and I still trust each other.
Maybe.
But I think
Immortal Luo Ge
will only believe what he sees
and hears.
Master.
You are awake.
Ge.
You actually
used your thousand-year spiritual power to save me?
Don't you know how important your responsibility is?
How could you waste this thousand-year spiritual power
on me?
You are like my father.
You taught me and protected me since I was a kid,
so now I must save you
and try my best
to seek justice for you.
Immortal Master,
Who is the person that hurt you?
We're looking into this.
It was her.
Liu Shao.
How dare you!
If it wasn't for Luo Ge,
I wouldn't be able to keep you alive.
How dare you come here to meet me?
Are you saying
that Immortal cares about me?
Then why do you
still drive me away?
Do you know
that I like him so much?
I will take good care of him.
Demon!
How dare you seduce Immortal?
You can't stay here!
Don't be angry, Immortal Master.
The reason why I came to you today is
to tell you
that Immortal Luo Ge
was not seduced by me at all.
Therefore,
you don't have to conflict with him
because of me.
What do you mean?
You may not know
that when Lu Sheng ordered Lu Li to approach me,
he cast a Soul-Devouring Spell on Lu Li
in order to prevent Lu Li from falling in love with me.
Lu Li died because of me,
which made Luo Ge successfully return from tribulation.
Immortal Luo Ge
had got his appearance,
his heart,
and even one drop of his tear.
But he did not get
the Soul-Devouring Spell from Lu Li.
Immortal Master,
think about it.
Is there any trace
of Soul-Devouring Spell
on Luo Ge's body?
This...
How is that possible?
She had the breath
of Sun Spirit in her body.
I can't be wrong.
Ge,
I would swear by my thousand years of cultivation
that it must be her.
It was really her.
No way.
No...
That's impossible.
It can't be her.
Ge.
Seeing is believing.
I'm not too old
to tell real from fake.
Liu Shao was crazy about love.
She's no longer the girl who could stick to her heart
and cross the Bone Melting Pool.
Luo Ge?
No way.
Luo Ge.
Ge.
The feeling of getting what you want
seems to make you happy?
Anyway,
thank you.
Thanks to you for giving me
the debris of Liu Shao's Sun Spirit,
so I could impersonate Liu Shao
without being detected by Immortal Master.
It's just...
where did you
get this debris?
Last time,
she went to Demon Palace
with Luo Ge
and got drunk.
I was thinking
this would come in handy.
Look,
it turns out that I was right.
I don't understand
why you hate her so much.
My brother is the dignified Demon King in White.
He's handsome and gentle.
What is my brother not good enough for her?
Since this woman is so unwise,
there will be no harm in killing her.
Then congratulations.
Your goal
should be achieved in no time.
Immortal Master has really woken up?
Then
the truth will be revealed.
Liu Shao,
aren't you going to confess?
Are you saying I'm the killer?
I narrowly escaped death.
How could I frame you?
It was really you.
You looked so innocent before
that I really thought I've wronged you.
No.
I didn't do it.
Immortal Master saw you with his own eyes.
That could also be wrong.
There are so many talented people in Immortal Palace,
it's easy for any one of them
to impersonate me.
Immortal Master has seen the Sun Spirit in you.
You are the only one in this world
who has it.
So?
Are you trying to say it wasn't you?
Right.
It wasn't me.
Even if I am old,
I can still recognize the person
who tried to kill me.
You're just too old!
Stop!
Don't be rude to Immortal Master.
What?
I can't even explain myself
after you wronged me?
Liu Shao.
If it wasn't for Immortal Luo Ge exhausting his spiritual power to save Immortal Master,
Immortal Master may really not be able to wake up.
You keep saying you were wronged.
Do you think it's possible that Immortal Master suffered such serious injuries
just to wrong you?
I don't know what happened.
But I know
that I never did anything to harm Immortal Master.
Now the witness and evidence are all there.
Look around you,
who else dares to believe you.
Luo Ge,
do you believe me?
How dare you, a murderer,
call Immortal by his name directly?
You have no right
to tell others what to do here.
Ge,
I'm begging you.
You can't pamper her anymore.
Just punish her according to the law.
Liu Shao.
Think about it.
Where were you last night?
Can someone testify for you?
Would you believe me
if I said
that I was practicing Ice Spirit in the back mountain
last night?
Do you have witnesses?
What if I have no witness?
Immortal.
According to the regulations of Immortal Palace,
those who cause serious injuries
to the elders
shall be taken to the Land of Heaven's Punishment
and be executed by heavenly punishment.
Such punishments
are handled by Palace Wuxie.
Immortal,
please leave Liu Shao to me.
After the execution,
you can take back her Sun Spirit
and choose another upright and kind person
as its host.
Did you hear that?
Yes.
But I also said
that I have never been to Palace Wuji
before today,
nor have I left the back mountain.
Luo Ge.
♫On rainy days, wind blows smoke♫
I'll ask you one last time.
♫Into circles♫
Do you believe me?
♫On both sides, I'm chanting♫
You have to give me a reason to believe you.
♫The night is sleepless♫
♫The shadows of the moon are incomplete, and people are in love♫
♫A cocoon of shadows♫
Because Lu Li would always believe me.
♫Your promise, my fate♫
Even if he didn't believe his eyes
♫In spring, seasons changed♫
and ears,
he would always believe me.
♫But my heart is still the same♫
Ge.
♫Back to the sky, the clouds passing by♫
How can you allow her to lie to you here?
♫Is like the things we went through♫
♫Beside the lake, on the boat♫
♫The moment we passed each other♫
♫Can compare with the rest of my life♫
Lu Li is gone.
♫I look at my love and send it to the clouds outside the garden♫
So you don't love me
♫Looking at your ageless face at the end of the world♫
nor do you trust me.
Shut up!
Qiuxian.
Take her to the Land of Heaven's Punishment for execution.
♫You put the winter snow in your ears and can’t hear it♫
Yes.
♫When the flowers stop falling, you and I will miss each other♫
♫Everything in the world passes before understanding♫
Since you and I have known each other before,
♫After the missing, my face is still young♫
I'll keep your body intact.
You will be punished by Icy Nightmares,
and will die in agony in your nightmares.
♫The day the flowers fall in the garden, the day we meet♫
People always have to pay
♫If you see me for the first time in this life, I'll forever hold it in my heart♫
for what they do.
♫Get lost in your sky♫
It turns out
♫Whose wilderness♫
dying in the nightmare
♫Clouds billow up and fade away in the four seas♫
is your gift for me.
♫The mountains and rivers after the farewell♫
I would really like to appreciate you,
♫Silence♫
the supreme Immortal Luo Ge of the Three Realms.
♫Time sighs silently♫
♫Whose passing years♫
There's nothing
but only sorrow in my dead heart.
The truth is nothing to me.
Since Lu Li's gone,
nothing is worth it.
There's no need to feel sorry for her.
She deserved it.
Icy Nightmare.
I heard the pain of it
is not less than the Thunder Penalty.
It even lasts longer.
I didn't expect Luo Ge
to be so cruel.
He's even crueler
than the way he treated me last time.
All right.
Your wish has come true.
Now it's time for me to make requests.
Go ahead.
What do you want?
Help me get the Moon Sword.
Are you going to split the Four Seasons Monument
and release the demon heart of God of the Moonlight?
Something like that.
Do you think I'll agree?
Why not?
If you don't agree,
I will definitely tell Luo Ge something.
What did you say?
Immortal Master was assassinated,
and Liu Shao was identified as the murderer?
How is that possible?
How could Liu Shao kill someone?
No.
I have to ask my brother about these.
Seriously?
He actually put a ban on me
and kept me from going out.
What should I do?
How about I
ask Fu?
My little fairy is calling me.
Think about it carefully.
I believe
you will make a right decision.
I'll ignore Moon Sword for now.
The most important thing now
is that Liu Shao will be dead for sure.
Luo Ge.
I have already tried my best.
I actually checked
the three palaces,
including Palace Wuji where Immortal Master lives.
And I have checked all the roads
towards the back mountain.
But no one has seen Liu Shao
these days.
Someone must have seen her on her way back and forth,
if Liu Shao had come back from the back mountain that day.
The fact that no one has seen her
means it's likely
that she wasn't lying,
and she really didn't leave the back mountain.
So,
you also think there's something suspicious about this,
and
you don't think
Liu Shao would kill Immortal Master, right?
It was impossible
for her to do such a thing.
But there are many weird spells in the Three Realms
that can confuse people's minds.
Maybe she was used,
and she lost herself at the time.
But
we can't find anything right now.
And even if we found out something, it would be useless.
Icy Nightmare...
After 24 hours,
she will die due to the shattering of her energy pill,
but with much more pain than the way she would die in Thunder Penalty.
Actually,
you also want to
prove her innocence
within twenty-four hours, right?
After all,
if it was Heavenly Punishment,
she would have been reduced to ashes
twenty hours ago.
It has been twenty hours.
She might not even have a bone scum left.
I won't let her die.
This is him.
No, it's me...
Remember, I have a name.
Lu Li?
Take me home...
Lu Li.
Why don't you trust her?
Why did you hurt her?
Why don't you see our past memories
with your own eyes?
I will always trust you in the future.
Even if I don't believe my eyes and ears,
I will certainly believe you.
What happened to you?
Are you okay?
Don't make me worry about you.
I just
saw Lu Li's memories.
What did you say?
I said I believed her.
Do you think
my brother is unreasonable?
How could Liu Shao
assassinate Immortal Master Wanwu?
Also,
why did he lock me up here?
He really pissed me off.
Little fairy.
Don't worry.
I am already working on it.
I can definitely find a way
to break this forbidden spell
and let you go out to save her.
It's useless to read this.
You can't
undo my brother's forbidden spell.
Luo Ge is not here.
Now is the best opportunity.
I'll have to think of something else.
How about I pretend to be sick?
No.
I'll just pretend to faint.
In this case,
someone will notify my brother, right?
When I see him,
I'll definitely ask him about that.
Immortal Luo Ge
is probably not so easy to deceive.
The amount of water energy really did not meet my expectations.
If I forcefully break through the barrier,
I will definitely be seriously injured.
Will she
save me?
I can only take a risk.
Fu!
Fu, what happened to you?
I was too stupid
to break your brother's forbidden spell.
I am badly injured.
Can you save me?
Okay, wait for me.
I'll get someone to save you.
Don't call anyone.
You'll be implicated.
You can save me.
I...
You have Bone-Corroding Harp.
Bone-Corroding Harp?
Hadn't the Bone-Corroding Harp been broken long ago
and been kept in the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors treasury?
Bone-Corroding Harp
belongs to you.
It will follow your heart.
Call it.
How...
How is that possible, Fu?
Fu!
Fu.
You are saying
you remember something from your time in the human world?
Yes.
I believe the assassin wasn't Liu Wei.
But if she dies,
it will be too late.
What do you want to do?
Master.
You can't go in, Master.
Immortal won't see anyone today.
How can he not meet me?
I brought you something good for Liu Shao.
Let him in.
Greetings, Immortal.
I finally fulfilled Liu Shao's entrustment.
I've guarded this Weirui Grass for her
until it's grown up.
What did you say?
Liu Shao planted this grass?
Yes.
I said that the vitality of Weirui Grass
can cure
Immortal's problems during cultivation.
Regardless of her limping leg,
she desperately tried
to grow the grass
during the last three days of her stay here.
She is really amazing.
In order to obtain
the power of Yin and Yang that can make Weirui Grass sprout,
she worked hard to practice Ice Spirit.
I don't know
which bastard made up that Spirit.
The Yin and Yang were intertwined, the water and fire were incompatible.
That almost tortured her to death.
I didn't expect
that she really made it
and planted this grass in three days.
Would you believe me
if I said
that I was practicing Ice Spirit in the back mountain
last night?
So,
what Liu Shao said in the hall yesterday was true?
Has Liu Shao been in the back mountain for the past three days?
Of course.
She never left.
If it wasn't because
the time for her to leave has come,
she would have guarded the grass until it's grown,
and then brought it to Immortal herself.
Immortal.
Immortal?
What happened to him?
Liu Shao is too stubborn.
Why didn't she say anything?
Well...
What's wrong?
Luo Ge.
I just want to ask you,
do you trust me?
Sorry.
I'm late.
Immortal Luo Ge.
What are you doing?
Wan Sui proved
that it was not her who assassinated Immortal Master.
Wan Sui has such a good relationship with Liu Shao,
how could his words be used as testimony?
Senior,
I can also prove it.
LiuShao is now in the depths of a nightmare.
Unless someone wakes her up,
she will surely die in another hour
due to the rupture of her energy pill.
Immortal,
Palace Wuxie has its own rules.
Since Liu Shao has been handed over to Palace Wuxie for execution,
you can't take her away.
Luo Ge,
even if you enter the depths of her nightmare now,
I'm afraid there's nothing you can do.
You might not be able to come back too.
Liu Shao.
Liu Shao, wake up.
Do you remember me?
Liu Shao.
We either die together...
I'm Luo Ge.
or we go together.
We either die together...
Don't... don't leave me!
Liu Shao, wake up!
Do you know
that you will become a nightmare,
if you don't wake up?
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Lu Li.
Why are you here?
Luo Ge.
Let me ask you one last time,
do you trust me?
You have to give me a reason to trust you.
No.
♫In the sea of clouds, I looked at the reflection of the moon in the water♫
You don't believe me.
You never believed me.
You're not Lu Li.
♫I kept waiting and arched my palms into a circle♫
Lu Li died, all of this is fake.
This is not a dream,
I'm real.
♫The reflection gradually reminded me of our first meeting♫
The real Luo Ge
and the real Lu Li.
♫I can no longer tell the difference between wind and rain♫
♫Even if I get the volley sword♫
Luo Ge?
♫I can't forget you♫
♫Our destiny has been sealed long ago♫
Luo Ge.
I don't want to leave.
I want to stay by your side forever.
♫I have no other choice♫
♫Why have you been so far away from me every time♫
Then stay.
♫For billions of years♫
But
I don't want you
♫Can I use your hands to warm up the world again?♫
to get hurt.
♫A few hasty nights♫
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch, and watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
Be careful!
No!
It was Lu Li who trapped her.
Liu Shao.
All that you suffered in your nightmare
was because you didn't want to lose that person on the boat.
Do you know
who was on the boat?
It was Lu Li, I guess?
I want to get Lu Li back,
even if it's all in vain.
Lu Li believed me.
And Luo Ge didn't.
So I can only love Lu Li,
not Luo Ge,
even if I know
they are the same person.
No.
I believe you too,
just like Lu Li.
But...
I'm sorry that
I didn't protect you well.
What did you say?
I don't understand.
Liu Shao.
Lu Li is your nightmare,
and also mine.
The person you have been unwilling to lose is Lu Li.
And Lu Li...
is me.
He is also the heart
I have been afraid to face.
It turned out that no matter how I tried to escape,
I couldn't escape this heart.
From now on,
Luo Ge is Lu Li.
I will stand in front of you,
trust you
and protect you.
Because
I'm afraid
I can't escape this love anymore.
No...
This must be a dream.
Luo Ge would never say such things to me.
Whether it's a dream or not,
I will never leave you again.